crazyabouttv.com 2013-05-19

# CrazyAboutTV.com Privacy Policy

|     | 

**Privacy Policy**   
**CrazyAboutTV.com**

At CrazyAboutTV.com, we respect your privacy and make every effort to protect it while you are visiting our site. The vast majority of websites on the internet collect information about you when you visit. The information is generally utilized to provide the webmaster with information that enables them to better run their site. Another purpose for gathering information about you is to provide you with information aimed at your specific interests. The only piece of information we collect that may identify you personally is your IP address and the only reason we use that information is in the case of someone spamming our forum, hacking our site or engaging in some other unethical or illegal activity. In no case do we sell any information collected at our site to any third party. 

## Log Files:

The information we receive in our log files includes your IP address, your internet service provider, what browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited our site and what pages you visited throughout our site. 

## Cookies:

We do use cookies to store your username and password after you enter them at our [TV forums](http://www.crazyabouttv.com/TVshowtalk/index.php). Without these cookies you would have to re-enter that information every time you visited the forum. Our advertisers also use cookies to present you with ads that are most likely to interest you. If you have recently visited a site about Brazil for example, the cookies tell our advertisers that you might appreciate an ad from a travel site. For more information about how ad cookies work, visit the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

## You Can Disable Cookies:

Cookies are stored on your computer, not on our network but you can still turn ours and/or those of third-parties in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security if you wish. You can do this by turning them off for all sites or selectively. Be aware that if you do this it may prevent you from signing in to forums or participating in any other activities involving a log-in. While you will still see ads, ours and recommendations from shopping sites like Amazon, Best Buy, etc. will no longer be targeted to your interests. 

## Links to Other Sites:

We sometimes link to other sites. We have no control over the privacy policies of those sites. This privacy policy only applies to this site. If you leave our site you should read the privacy policy of the new site when you arrive there. 

## Contact Us:

If you have any questions about our privacy policy feel free to contact us at admin@crazyabouttv.com. Please do not spam our email. We cherish our privacy too.  [](http://www.facebook.com/CrazyAboutTV) Copyright © 1997-2013 CrazyAboutTV.com  
All rights reserved
